RG 003, New London County, County Court Files
Connecticut State Library
- Files, 1691-1855
  - 1801 (Box 251)
    - December, no docket (Ames-Button) (Box 255, Folder 24-25)
    - December, no docket (Capron-Woodward) (Box 256, Folder 1-8)
  - 1802 (Box 256)
    - March, no. 1-212 (Box 256, Folder 9-24)
    - March, no docket (Ash-Carpenter) (Box 256, Folder 25)
    - March, no docket (Chappell-York) (Box 257, Folder 1-7)
    - June, no. 1-226 (Box 257, Folder 8-25)
    - June, no. 227-295 (Box 258, Folder 1-7)
    - June, no docket (Avery-Yeomans) (Box 258, Folder 8-16)
    - November, no. 1-135 (Box 258, Folder 17-25)
    - November, no. 135-330 (Box 259, Folder 1-15)
    - November, no docket (Avery-Woodworth) (Box 259, Folder 16-23)
  - 1803 (Box 259)
    - March, no. 1-31 (Box 259, Folder 24)
    - March, no. 32-160 (Box 260, Folder 1-10)
    - March, no docket (Babcock-Williams) (Box 260, Folder 11-15)
    - June, no. 1-115 (Box 260, Folder 16-23)
    - June, no. 116-295 (Box 261, Folder 1-11)
    - June, no docket (Allyn-Young) (Box 261, Folder 12-19)
    - November, no. 7-63 (Box 261, Folder 20-22)
    - November, no. 64-244 (Box 262, Folder 1-12)
    - November, no docket (Abell-Woodward) (Box 262, Folder 13-21)
  - 1804 (Box 262)
    - February, no. 1-36 (Box 262, Folder 22-23)
    - February, no. 38-172 (Box 263, Folder 1-9)
    - February, no docket (Aaron-York) (Box 263, Folder 10-13)
    - June, no. 2-115 (Box 263, Folder 14-24)
    - June, no. 116-263 (Box 264, Folder 1-10)
    - June, no docket (Ame-York) (Box 264, Folder 11-17)
    - November, no. 2-90 (Box 264, Folder 18-24)
    - November, no. 94-244 (Box 265, Folder 1-13)
    - November, no docket (Abbott-Wyles) (Box 265, Folder 14-21)
  - 1805 (Box 265)
    - March, no. 5-73 (Box 265, Folder 22-25)
    - March, no. 74-179 (Box 266, Folder 1-6)
    - March, no docket (Andrews-Worden) (Box 266, Folder 7-11)
    - June, no. 1-183 (Box 266, Folder 12-24)
    - June, no. 186-244 (Box 267, Folder 1-4)
    - June, no docket (Abel-York) (Box 267, Folder 5-12)
    - December, no. 11-202 (Box 267, Folder 13-23)
    - December, no. 204-254 (Box 268, Folder 1-4)
    - December, no docket (Atwell-Woodbridge) (Box 268, Folder 5-11)
  - 1806 (Box 268)
    - March, no. 1-156 (Box 268, Folder 12-20)
    - March, no docket (Armstrong-Gray) (Box 268, Folder 21-22)
    - March, no docket (Handy-Wright) (Box 269, Folder 1-4)
    - June, no. 2-274 (Box 269, Folder 5-21)
    - June, no docket (Ayers-Woodward) (Box 270, Folder 1-6)
    - November, no. 2-287 (Box 270, Folder 7-21)
    - November, no. 291-344 (Box 271, Folder 1-3)
    - November, no docket (Allen-Willson) (Box 271, Folder 4-12)
  - 1807 (Box 271)
    - March, no. 3-150 (Box 271, Folder 13-20)
    - March, no. 151-272, no docket (Box 272, Folder 1-6)
    - June, no. 5-199 (Box 272, Folder 7-20)
    - June, no. 200-487 (Box 273, Folder 1-20)
    - December, no. 1-14 (Box 273, Folder 21)
    - December, no. 16-323 (Box 274, Folder 1-20)
    - December, no. 324-443 (Box 275, Folder 1-9)
  - 1808 (Box 275)
    - March, no. 1-171 (Box 275, Folder 10-21)
    - March, no. 172-368, no docket (Box 276, Folder 1-14)
    - June, no. 3-83 (Box 277, Folder 15-21)
    - June, no. 88-428 (Box 277, Folder 1-21)
    - June, no. 429-758 (Box 278, Folder 1-21)
    - November, no. 4-366 (Box 279, Folder 1-20)
    - November, no. 367-545 (Box 280, Folder 1-13)
  - 1809 (Box 280)
    - March, no. 6-132 (Box 280, Folder 14-21)
    - March, no. 133-307, no docket (Box 281, Folder 1-13)
    - June, no. 1-115 (Box 281, Folder 14-21)
    - June, no. 116-356 (Box 282, Folder 1-20)
    - June, no. 359-391 (Box 283, Folder 1-2)
    - June, no docket (Abel-Yelverton) (Box 283, Folder 3-12)
    - December, no. 3-146 (Box 283, Folder 13-22)
    - December, no. 147-359 (Box 284, Folder 1-16)
    - December, no docket (Adams-Young) (Box 284, Folder 17-22)
  - 1810
    - March, no. 1-274 (Box 285, Folder 1-16)
    - June, no. 1-99 (Box 285, Folder 17-20)
    - June, no. 100-442 (Box 286, Folder 1-20)
    - June, no docket (Box 286, Folder 21)
    - December, no. 1-346 (Box 287, Folder 1-17)
    - December, no. 347-398 (Box 288, Folder 1-3)
  - 1811 (Box 288)
    - March, no. 1-249 (Box 288, Folder 1-17)
    - June (Allyn-Perkins) (Box 289, Folder 1-20)
    - June (Phelps-Woodbridge) (Box 290, Folder 1-12)
    - December (Allen-Deming) (Box 290, Folder 13-20)
    - December (Denison-Russell) (Box 291, Folder 1-21)
    - December (Scovell-York) (Box 292, Folder 1-10)
  - 1812 (Box 292)
    - March, no. 4-110 (Box 292, Folder 11-20)
    - March, no. 111-343 (Box 293, Folder 1-21)
    - June, no. 1-224 (Box 294, Folder 1-20)
    - June, no. 225-347 (Box 295, Folder 1-13)
    - December, no. 2-100 (Box 295, Folder 14-21)
    - December, no. 101-301 (Box 296, Folder 1-22)
    - December, no. 302-337 (Box 297, Folder 1-4)
  - 1813 (Box 297)
    - March, no. 1-186 (Box 297, Folder 5-21)
    - March, no. 188-293 (Box 298, Folder 1-9)
    - June, no. 9-183 (Box 298, Folder 10-21)
    - June, no. 184-276 (Box 299, Folder 1-10)
    - December, no. 1-87 (Box 299, Folder 11-20)
    - December, no. 88-267 (Box 300, Folder 1-20)
    - December, no. 268-307 (Box 301, Folder 1-4)
  - 1814 (Box 301)
    - March, no. 2-159 (Box 301, Folder 5-21)
    - March, no. 160-202 (Box 302, Folder 1-4)
    - June, no. 1-129 (Box 302, Folder 5-20)
    - June, no. 130-253 (Box 303, Folder 1-11)
    - December, no. 1-124 (Box 304, Folder 12-21)
    - December, no. 125-321 (Box 304, Folder 1-21)
    - December, no. 322-329 (Box 305, Folder 1-2)
  - 1815 (Box 305)
    - March, no. 1-182 (Box 305, Folder 3-20)
    - March, no. 183-286 (Box 306, Folder 1-12)
    - June, no. 5-54 (Box 306, Folder 13-19)
    - June, no. 55-264 (Box 307, Folder 1-20)
    - June, no. 266-319 (Box 308, Folder 1-8)
    - December, no. 1-150 (Box 308, Folder 9-20)
    - December, no. 151-330 (Box 309, Folder 1-20)
    - December, no. 331-363 (Box 310, Folder 1-2)
  - 1816 (Box 310, Folder 300)
    - March, no. 2-160 (Box 310, Folder 3-20)
    - March, no. 161-368 (Box 311, Folder 1-20)
    - June, no. 3-203 (Box 312, Folder 1-20)
    - June, no. 204-377 (Box 313, Folder 1-20)
    - June, no. 378-434 (Box 314, Folder 1-7)
    - June, no docket (Box 314, Folder 8)
    - December, 1-113 (Box 314, Folder 9-20)
    - December, no. 115-341 (Box 315, Folder 1-20)
    - December, no. 342-530 (Box 316, Folder 1-19)
  - 1817
    - March, no. 3-205 (Box 317, Folder 1-19)
    - March, no. 206-399 (Box 318, Folder 1-20)
    - March, no. 400-501 (Box 319, Folder 1-9)
    - June (Armstrong-Frink) (Box 320, Folder 1-20)
    - June, (Gardner-Schofield) (Box 320, Folder 1-20)
    - June (Sheffield-Young) (Box 321, Folder 1-12)
    - December (Abell-Cross) (Box 321, Folder 13-21)
    - December (Darrow-Richards) (Box 322, Folder 1-21)
    - December (Ripley-Yerrington) (Box 323, Folder 1-10)
  - 1818 (Box 323)
    - March (Abell-Hull) (Box 323, Folder 11-21)
    - March (Huntington-Wright) (Box 324, Folder 1-18)
    - June (Abel-Billings) (Box 324, Folder 19-20)
    - June (Brainard-Utley) (Box 325, Folder 1-20)
    - June (Way-York) (Box 326, Folder 1-3)
    - December (Anderson-Page) (Box 326, Folder 4-21)
    - December (Palmer-Wright) (Box 327, Folder 1-10)
  - 1819 (Box 327)
    - March (Abel-Hull) (Box 327, Folder 11-21)
    - March (Huntington-Yeomans) (Box 328, Folder 1-13)
    - June (Aldrich-Hart) (Box 328, Folder 14-20)
    - June (Harvey-Woodward) (Box 329, Folder 1-13)
    - December (Allen-Cole) (Box 329, Folder 14-20)
    - December (Comstock-Slate) (Box 330, Folder 1-20)
    - December (Smith-York) (Box 331, Folder 1-8)
  - 1820 (Box 331)
    - March (Abell-Heath) (Box 331, Folder 9-20)
    - March (Hempsted-York) (Box 332, Folder 1-18)
    - June (Adams-Baldwin) (Box 332, Folder 19-20)
    - June (Barnes-Smith) (Box 333, Folder 1-21)
    - June (Spalding-Young) (Box 334, Folder 1-7)
    - December (Allen-Holdridge) (Box 334, Folder 8-21)
    - December (Holmes-Vibber) (Box 335, Folder 1-20)
    - December (Wait-Young) (Box 336, Folder 1-2)
  - 1821 (Box 336)
    - March (Ackley-Tate) (Box 336, Folder 3-21)
    - March (Thomas-Young) (Box 337, Folder 1-3)
    - June (Andrus-Palmer) (Box 337, Folder 4-20)
    - June (Palmer-Year) (Box 338, Folder 1-9)
    - November (Amers-Perkins) (Box 338, Folder 10-20)
    - November (Perigo-Wright) (Box 339, Folder 1-9)
  - 1822 (Box 339)
    - March (Averill-Smith) (Box 339, Folder 10-21)
    - March (State-Woodbridge) (Box 340, Folder 1-3)
    - June (Armstrong-Williams) (Box 340, Folder 4-20)
    - November, no. 1-284 (Box 341, Folder 1-16)
    - November, no docket (Appleman-Williams) (Box 341, Folder 17-18)
  - 1823 (Box 341)
    - March (Andrus-Cleland) (Box 341, Folder 19-21)
    - March (Clement-Ward) (Box 342, Folder 1-13)
    - June (Abel-Dolbear) (Box 342, Folder 14-20)
    - June (Douglas-Woodworth) (Box 343, Folder 1-13)
    - November (Amy-Hart) (Box 343, Folder 14-20)
    - November (Hartshorn-Yeomans) (Box 344, Folder 1-17)
  - 1824 (Box 344)
    - March (Adams-Burling) (Box 344, Folder 18-21)
    - March (Casey-Worden) (Box 345, Folder 1-20)
    - June (Albee-Turner) (Box 346, Folder 1-20)
    - June (Waite-Wyles) (Box 347, Folder 1-2)
    - November (Amidown-Wyse) (Box 347, Folder 3-21)
  - 1825
    - March (Avery-Williams) (Box 348, Folder 1-12)
    - June (Addison-Minard) (Box 3488, Folder 13-21)
    - June (Minor-Wheeler) (Box 349, Folder 1-10)
    - November (Stanton-York) (Box 350, Folder 1-6)
  - 1826 (Box 350)
    - March (Allyn-Warren) (Box 350, Folder 7-20)
    - March (Way-Young) (Box 351, Folder 1)
    - June (Anderson-Young) (Box 351, Folder 2-21)
    - November (Anderson-Winthrop) (Box 352, Folder 1-24)
  - 1827
    - March (Avery-Young) (Box 353, Folder 1-21)
    - June (Alexander-Avery) (Box 353, Folder 22)
    - June (Babcock-Whittelsey) (Box 354, Folder 1-24)
    - November (Allen-Woodworth) (Box 355, Folder 1-22)
  - 1828
    - March (Adams-Wright) (Box 356, Folder 1-18)
    - June (Armstrong-Hall) (Box 356, Folder 19-22)
    - June (Hanover-Williams) (Box 357, Folder 1-9)
    - November (Armstrong-Olin) (Box 357, Folder 10-22)
    - November (Palmer-Wolf) (Box 358, Folder 1-9)
  - 1829 (Box 358)
    - March (Adams-Ripley) (Box 358, Folder 10-23)
    - March (Ripley-Williams) (Box 359, Folder 1-8)
    - June (Agnew-Prentice) (Box 359, Folder 9-23)
    - June (Randall-Wilson) (Box 360, Folder 1-5)
    - November (Armstrong-State) (Box 360, Folder 6-23)
    - November (State-Wright) (Box 361, Folder 1-7)
  - 1830 (Box 361)
    - March (Alexander-Mason) (Box 361, Folder 8-23)
    - March (Mason-York) (Box 362, Folder 1-12)
    - June (Allyn-Hewit) (Box 362, Folder 13-23)
    - June (Hill-Wright) (Box 363, Folder 1-16)
    - November (Adams-Cox) (Box 363, Folder 17-22)
    - November (Craft-Woodward) (Box 364, Folder 1-22)
  - 1831
    - February (Allen-Wyles) (Box 365, Folder 1-13)
    - June (Allyn-Lord) (Box 365, Folder 14-23)
    - June (Lord-Wright) (Box 366, Folder 1-14)
    - November (Avery-Fitch) (Box 366, Folder 15-20)
    - November (Fitch-Wood) (Box 367, Folder 1-18)
  - 1832 (Box 367)
    - February (Avery-Darrow) (Box 367, Folder 19-22)
    - February (Darrow-Wright) (Box 368, Folder 1-16)
    - June (Allen-Darrow) (Box 368, Folder 17-22)
    - June (Darrow-Williams) (Box 369, Folder 1-15)
    - November (Abel-Chapman) (Box 369, Folder 16-22)
    - November (Chapman-Thames Bank) (Box 370, Folder 1-22)
    - November (Tiffany-Woodruff) (Box 371, Folder 1-5)
  - 1833 (Box 371)
    - February (Adams-Mason) (Box 371, Folder 6-22)
    - February (Mather-Yerington) (Box 372, Folder 1-12)
    - June (Allen-Ladd) (Box 372, Folder 13-22)
    - June (Ladd-Wright) (Box 373, Folder 1-13)
    - November (Adams-Fanning) (Box 373, Folder 14-22)
    - November (Fitch-Wyles) (Box 374, Folder 1-20)
  - 1834 (Box 374)
    - February (Albertson-Armstrong) (Box 374, Folder 21)
    - February (Avery-Stowel) (Box 375, Folder 1-22)
    - February (Strong-Winship) (Box 376, Folder 1-9)
    - June (Adams-L'Hommedieu) (Box 376, Folder 10-23)
    - June (Lester-York) (Box 377, Folder 1-15)
    - November (Abel-Eggleston) (Box 377, Folder 16-21)
    - November (Eldredge-Wheeler) (Box 378, Folder 1-21)
    - November (Wheeler-Wyles) (Box 379, Folder 1-3)
  - 1835 (Box 379)
    - February (Adams-Morgan) (Box 379, Folder 4-21)
    - February (Morrell-Wilson) (Box 380, Folder 1-15)
    - June (Ashby-Darrow) (Box 380, Folder 16-21)
    - June (Dart-State) (Box 381, Folder 1-21)
    - June (State-Young) (Box 382, Folder 1-5)
    - November, no. 2-160 (Box 382, Folder 6-21)
    - November, no. 161-297 (Box 383, Folder 1-14)
  - 1836 (Box 383)
    - February, no. 1-96 (Box 383, Folder 15-21)
    - February, no. 97-275 (Box 384, Folder 1-17)
    - June, no. 3-46 (Box 384, Folder 18-21)
    - June, no. 51-282 (Box 385, Folder 1-19)
    - November, no. 2-19 (Box 385, Folder 20-21)
    - November, no. 23-266 (Box 386, Folder 1-21)
    - November, no. 267-300 (Box 387, Folder 1-3)
  - 1837 (Box 387)
    - February, no. 1-223 (Box 387, Folder 4-20)
    - June, no. 5-46 (Box 387, Folder 21-24)
    - June, no. 50-306 (Box 388, Folder 1-19)
    - June, no. 307-350 (Box 389, Folder 1-2)
    - November, no. 1-218 (Box 389, Folder 3-19)
    - November, no. 220-334 (Box 390, Folder 1-8)
  - 1838 (Box 390)
    - February, no. 3-198 (Box 390, Folder 9-19)
    - February, no. 199-258 (Box 391, Folder 1-4)
    - June, no. 3-279 (Box 391, Folder 5-20)
    - June, no. 280-314 (Box 392, Folder 1-3)
    - November, no. 2-285 (Box 392, Folder 4-18)
  - 1839 (Box 392)
    - February, no. 4-40 (Box 392, Folder 19-20)
    - February, no. 49-272 (Box 393, Folder 1-14)
    - June, no. 1-72 (Box 393, Folder 15-20)
    - June, no. 73-230 (Box 394, Folder 1-10)
    - November, no. 1-149 (Box 394, Folder 11-20)
    - November, no. 150-306 (Box 395, Folder 1-13)
  - 1840 (Box 395)
    - February, no. 2-63 (Box 395, Folder 14-20)
    - February, no. 64-233 (Box 396, Folder 1-14)
    - June, no. 1-91 (Box 397, Folder 15-20)
    - June, no. 92-264 (Box 397, Folder 1-16)
    - November, no. 1-38 (Box 397, Folder 17-19)
    - November, no. 39-254 (Box 398, Folder 1-17)
  - 1841
    - February, no. 5-221 (Box 399, Folder 1-18)
    - June, no. 1-211 (Box 400, Folder 1-20)
    - June, no. 212-242 (Box 401, Folder 1-4)
    - November, no. 1-168 (Box 401, Folder 5-20)
    - November, no. 169-240 (Box 402, Folder 1-7)
  - 1842 (Box 402)
    - February, no. 1-188 (Box 402, Folder 8-20)
    - June, no. 5-232 (Box 403, Folder 1-18)
    - November, no. 5-15 (Box 403, Folder 19-20)
    - November, no. 16-225 (Box 404, Folder 1-20)
  - 1843
    - February, no. 3-195 (Box 405, Folder 1-12)
    - June, no. 2-110 (Box 405, Folder 13-18)
    - June, no. 112-196 (Box 406, Folder 1-7)
    - November, no. 3-130 (Box 406, Folder 8-20)
    - November, no. 131-238 (Box 407, Folder 1-8)
  - 1844 (Box 407)
    - February, no. 3-184 (Box 407, Folder 9-19)
    - June, no. 3-204 (Box 408, Folder 1-15)
    - November, no. 2-50 (Box 408, Folder 16-19)
    - November, no. 51-263 (Box 409, Folder 1-8)
  - 1845 (Box 409)
    - February, no. 1-335 (Box 409, Folder 9-20)
    - February, miscellaneous (Box 410, Folder 1)
    - June, no. 22-459 (Box 410, Folder 2-12)
    - November, no. 27-480 (Box 410, Folder 13-20)
    - November, no. 481-585 (Box 411, Folder 1-6)
  - 1846 (Box 411)
    - February, no. 5-704 (Box 411, Folder 7-14)
    - June, no. 3-698 (Box 411, Folder 15-19)
    - June, no. 670-780 (Box 412, Folder 1-6)
    - November, no. 25-969 (Box 412, Folder 7-19)
  - 1847
    - February, no. 1-220 (Box 413, Folder 1-13)
    - June, no. 13-278 (Box 413, Folder 14-20)
    - June, no. 279-343 (Box 414, Folder 1-4)
    - July, no. 106-349 (Box 414, Folder 5)
    - November, no. 2-523 (Box 414, Folder 6-20)
    - November, no. 524-579 (Box 415, Folder 1-3)
  - 1848 (Box 415)
    - February, no. 21-679 (Box 415, Folder 4-13)
    - June, no. 38-686 (Box 415, Folder 14-18)
    - June, no. 687-860 (Box 416, Folder 1-10)
    - July, no. 58-842 (Box 416, Folder 11)
    - September, no. 75-865 (Box 416, Folder 12)
    - November, no. 37-847 (Box 416, Folder 13-19)
    - November, no. 858-1001 (Box 417, Folder 1-10)
    - November, miscellaneous (Box 417, Folder 11)
    - December, no. 1003-1018 (Box 417, Folder 12)
  - 1849 (Box 417)
    - February, no. 7-130 (Box 417, Folder 13-20)
    - February, no. 131-194 (Box 418, Folder 1-5)
    - June, no. 5-347 (Box 418, Folder 6-18)
    - June, no. 355-395 (Box 419, Folder 1-5)
    - July-September (Box 419, Folder 6)
    - November, no. 2-499 (Box 419, Folder 7-19)
    - November, no. 500-662 (Box 420, Folder 1-14)
  - 1850 (Box 420)
    - February, no. 53-620 (Box 420, Folder 15-19)
    - February, no. 650-849 (Box 420, Folder 1-13)
    - March, no. 121-761 (Box 421, Folder 14)
    - June, no. 17-710 (Box 421, Folder 15-19)
    - June, no. 714-998 (Box 422, Folder 1-12)
    - November, no. 4-155 (Box 422, Folder 12-21)
    - November, no. 156-337 (Box 423, Folder 1-15)
  - 1851 (Box 423)
    - February, no. 6-289 (Box 423, Folder 16-20)
    - February, no. 292-421 (Box 424, Folder 1-9)
    - April, no. 51-442 (Box 424, Folder 10-11)
    - June, no. 1-507 (Box 424, Folder 12-21)
    - June, no. 508-550 (Box 425, Folder 1-4)
    - November, no. 22-701 (Box 425, Folder 5-20)
    - November, no. 702-753 (Box 426, Folder 1-7)
  - 1852 (Box 426)
    - February, no. 2-213 (Box 426, Folder 8-19)
    - February, no. 214-314 (Box 427, Folder 1-11)
    - June, no. 1-331 (Box 427, Folder 12-20)
    - June, no. 332-481 (Box 428, Folder 1-11)
    - November, no. 10-504 (Box 428, Folder 12-21)
    - November, no. 505-706 (Box 429, Folder 1-14)
  - 1853 (Box 429)
    - February, no. 42-638 (Box 429, Folder 15-21)
    - February, no. 639-815 (Box 430, Folder 1-11)
    - June, no. 14-886 (Box 430, Folder 12-21)
    - June, no. 887-982 (Box 431, Folder 1-5)
    - November, no. 1-266 (Box 431, Folder 6-21)
    - November, no. 267-288 (Box 432, Folder 1)
  - 1854 (Box 432)
    - February, no. 13-437 (Box 432, Folder 2-16)
    - June, no. 12-240 (Box 432, Folder 17-20)
    - June, no. 264-564 (Box 433, Folder 1-13)
    - November, no. 19-571 (Box 433, Folder 14-20)
    - November, no. 573-706 (Box 434, Folder 1-7)
  - 1855 (Box 434)
    - February, no. 8-768 (Box 434, Folder 8-21)
    - February, no. 769-797 (Box 435, Folder 1-2)
    - June, no. 142-935 (Box 435, Folder 3-10)